[{"answer": " Excuse me, Linda?  Do you have a sec", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Sure.  Whats up", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Excuse me, Linda?  Do you have a sec", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well, I was just in the middle of making copies for my presentation thi", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Sure.  Whats up", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Sure.  Whats wrong with it", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Well, I was just in the middle of making copies for my presentation thi", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I dont know.  First, it was printing bad copies.  The print was really light.  Then", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Sure.  Whats wrong with it", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " OK, lets go take a look at it", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 25, "question": " I dont know.  First, it was printing bad copies.  The print was really light.  Then", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": "Oh, thank you so much", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " OK, lets go take a look at it", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " All right.  See this light here on the front", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Oh, thank you so much", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " uh-huh", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " All right.  See this light here on the front", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " That indicates where the paper is jammed.  So if you just tap your finger on th", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 32, "question": " uh-huh", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 36, "question": " That indicates where the paper is jammed.  So if you just tap your finger on th", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " So it says open tray 2 and remove jammed paper.  Go ahead and pull tray ", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " All right.  Its open", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " So it says open tray 2 and remove jammed paper.  Go ahead and pull tray ", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Do you see any stuck paper in there", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " All right.  Its open", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I see a crumpled piece at the back", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Do you see any stuck paper in there", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Go ahead and just pull it out.  Just give it a good yank", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I see a crumpled piece at the back", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Got it", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Go ahead and just pull it out.  Just give it a good yank", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Ok, close the tray now", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Got it", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Did that clear the jam", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Ok, close the tray now", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " The light is gone from the screen here, so that means that the jam is fixed", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Did that clear the jam", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Thank goodness", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 49, "question": " The light is gone from the screen here, so that means that the jam is fixed", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " There is something else though", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Thank goodness", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " What", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 51, "question": " There is something else though", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " See this flashing light that says toner", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " See this flashing light that says toner", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " That means the toner cartridge is low.  Its running out of ink.  Thats why you", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Can we replace it", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 58, "question": " That means the toner cartridge is low.  Its running out of ink.  Thats why you", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " For now we can just shake up the cartridge and it should fix the problem for ", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Can we replace it", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " How do we do that", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " For now we can just shake up the cartridge and it should fix the problem for ", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Open up the front of the copier and slide the toner cartridge out.  Got it", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " How do we do that", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Yup", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Open up the front of the copier and slide the toner cartridge out.  Got it", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " OK.  Now, just shake it up.  Be careful not to get ink on your clothes though", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Yup", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK.  Now, just shake it up.  Be careful not to get ink on your clothes though", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Now just slide the cartridge back in and close up the front of the machine.  I", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 71, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " The copier is starting again.  Its working", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Now just slide the cartridge back in and close up the front of the machine.  I", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Good job", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 75, "question": " The copier is starting again.  Its working", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thank you so much for showing me how to fix it, Linda!  Ive never used thi", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Good job", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " No problem.  Its always causing problems!  Ill call the copier company an", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Thank you so much for showing me how to fix it, Linda!  Ive never used thi", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thanks again", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 84, "question": " No problem.  Its always causing problems!  Ill call the copier company an", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  And good luck with your presentation", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thanks again", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "02-06", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Youre welcome.  And good luck with your presentation", "qSentId": 85}]
